What is love?
Love is an act of bravery.
What if she doesn't like me?
What if she does?
What if she's now ready
to open her heart to you?
Ours was a love story like no other.
This story is not about
our "happily ever after".
Take a leap of faith, Mr. Herrera.
Maybe she's just waiting for you.
Hey, when will you wake up?
I'm going to get up.
Get up or you will get it from me
if I am late.
Do you honestly think
that I dream of working for my dad?
Mrs. Herrera...
Miss Marquez, where's my son?
And what happened?
The doctors are already attending to him.
Let's just wait for the doctor
so he can explain to you
Dex's current situation.
What happened?
I am so sorry, Mrs. Herrera.
I was watching him,
but I had to go to the office to double-check
if I had your numbers right,
to make sure you will pick him up.
Unfortunately, the guard didn't see
that he had gone out.
Joyce.
What happened? Where's Dex?
Where were you?
You're supposed to pick Dex up!
Joyce...
Answer me!
Joyce, I couldn't leave soon...
Where were you?
- Where were you?
- Joyce, Joyce.
- Joyce...
- Where were you?
Where were you?
Joyce, sorry.
Sorry.
My son.
It's your fault
that your son had an accident.
But being an irresponsible father
is your biggest fault.
Dad, please, I'm begging you.
Only you can help me and Dex.
Dad, please, I'm begging you... Dad.
Dad.
Of course, I will help you.
But I hope you learn your lesson.
I told you many times over.
Stop with your illusion of becoming a writer.
You can't make money off of writing.
You break your back working,
but you're neglecting your family.
The problem with you is...
that you think
I am the antagonist in your story.
If you only listened to me
and continued working for me,
you could have had a stable life.
You'd have money to support your family.
You'd have time to care for your child.
I've already deposited money to the hospital.
And I have settled everything needed
for Dex's surgery.
Keep that money for now,
so at least you have cash on you.
Joyce...
Joyce, I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
After the operation,
Dex has to stay in the recovery room first.
And then he'll get transferred
to a regular room.
We can be by his side tomorrow.
Go home for now.
We'll just call you if there's an update.
I'll stay here for now.
Hon...
Don't you feel guilty?
You have no time for your son and for Joyce.
Is that the life you want for them?
I promised your mother
that I will give you a good life.
But what happened?
You have turned out to be
my biggest disappointment.
Your mother will never forgive me.
Write everything you want to say.
That way, I will know
what's inside your heart.
Because I will make
all your wishes come true.
Dear, Mom... It's me.
I hope you're here.
I wish you were still alive
so that I could personally apologize.
For I have become a disappointment.
But I will feel shame if you can see me now.
And I will feel ashamed to face you.
I really tried, I promise.
But I failed.
And I failed miserably.
My son is suffering because of me.
Because of my shortcomings as a father.
Worse, I hurt the person I love.
I wasn't able to be a good husband to her.
I wasn't able to give them a good life.
Dad was right.
I shouldn't have been a part of Joyce
and my son's life.
I shouldn't have dragged them down
because of my weakness
so that they wouldn't have suffered
because of my failures.
If only I could undo the past...
If only I could turn back time.
I wish Joyce could be happy.
If I could rewrite my story,
I wouldn't have followed her.
I shouldn't have come into her life.
I shouldn't have involved other people.
Take a leap of faith.
Where am I?
Good morning, Sir.
Are you ready for today?
Where am I? What am I doing here?
Engineer William Herrera.
I had a hunch you went drinking last night
and I knew where to find you.
Well, also last night,
you were with your girlfriend.
She left early today.
So I'm assuming you were
basically doing boyfriend-girlfriend stuff.
What did you say?
Engineer William Herrera?
What are you saying? And, girlfriend?
Hey, I'm already married!
And...
why am I naked?
What did you do to me?
Excuse me, Sir!
Are you insinuating
that I did something unpleasant to you?
Please!
I've been your executive assistant for years!
I've always been professional.
Plus, knowing you,
you will never allow
relationships between employees.
Not to mention,
you like sleeping without a shirt on.
Did my dad order you to do this?
Tell me, is this a prank?
Sir, you're more of a prankster than me.
So I suggest you drop the innocent act.
If you don't,
you'll be late for your first meeting.
Dex!
Dex.
Sir!
Taxi!
- Boss, to City General.
- Sir, where are you going?
- Sir, wait!
- Let's go.
Sir!
What's going on with him?
Are you okay, sir?
Mister, do you have a phone?
Here it is, sir. Do you need to borrow it?
Thank you.
Sorry, the subscriber cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
No.
I can't contact her.
Seems like you had a long night, sir.
It's even worse.
I don't remember anything.
So don't party too much, sir.
You can be forgetful
when you're having too much fun.
Actually...
Mister, I'm going to ask you a favor.
I don't have my wallet with me.
But don't worry.
I'll pay you once I see my wife.
She's in the hospital.
She's looking after our son.
Mister, please trust me.
I'm not lying to you.
I really do not know what happened.
I can't remember anything.
The problem is I don't recall anything.
The last memory I have is...
Dad was right.
I shouldn't have been
part of Joyce's and my son's life.
If only I could erase the past...
If only I could turn back the time.
Who are you?
My last memory is...
I was in the house.
I can't remember
how I ended up in that building.
Ma'am.
- Yes, sir?
- How is my son's surgery?
Is he already transferred to a regular room?
What is your son's name?
Dexter Herrera.
Let me check, sir.
What's his name again?
Dexter Herrera. I'm his father.
My name is William Herrera.
I'm sorry, sir,
but your son's name is not in our records.
What are you saying?
Ma'am, can you please check again?
I'm sure you're mistaken.
What's the problem?
His son's name is not in our records.
What do you mean there's no record?
- He's really not here.
- I can't be wrong.
We brought our son here!
He had surgery
because of his injuries, remember?
Are you joking?
You're not funny!
- Sir, he's really not here.
- Sir, you need to calm down.
Calm down?
You're telling me my son's not here.
How can I calm down?
He's really not here.
No! Joyce!
- Joyce!
- Sir, calm down!
- Calm down my foot!
- Sir, your son's name is not here!
Joyce!
Sir!
- Where are you?
- Sir!
- Dex!
- Sir.
- Sir, he's really not here!
- Dex!
- Sir!
Where's my son?
Did you transfer him to another room?
Or has he been discharged?
- He's not here.
- Tell me!
Explain it to me! Where's my son?
He's really not here.
Where's my son?
Are you okay, sir?
How did my son suddenly disappear
from that hospital?
Maybe we went to the wrong hospital.
I know which hospital I left my son at.
Sorry, Mister.
Maybe it's better
if you'll bring me
to our house in Sto. Cristo instead.
Maybe they already went home.
At least I can finally pay you.
Okay, sir. No problem.
You can drop me off here.
Okay.
Mister, please, wait for me.
- I'll get some money.
- Okay, sir.
Wait a second.
Hon, I'm glad
Dex got discharged from the hospital.
Hon.
Hey!
Why are you hugging my wife?
Who are you? How did you get in here?
What do you mean who am I?
Who are you? Why are you in our house?
Hey, hey! Don't come near me!
- Come here, you pervert!
- Pervert?
- I'm not a pervert!
- Come here, you pervert!
What are you talking about?
I'm not a pervert!
Come here! Come here!
Here's a snow cabbage!
Come here, pervert!
Wait! Let's talk it out.
Let's talk it out.
- Mister!
- Hey!
Come back here!
Mister, start the car!
- Hurry up!
- Hey, hey, mister!
Hey! Mister, why did you leave me?
Come here!
I'll kill you!
Hey, hey!
- That's a pervert!
- Wait, wait.
I'm not a pervert!
- Boss, boss... wait, wait!
- Stop him!
Wait, boss. Let's talk it out.
- You're a pervert!
- I'm not a pervert!
That's our house!
- Why are you in our house?
- Beat him up!
Where's Joyce? Where's Dex? What's going on?
- Pervert!
- Hey!
You're lucky the village cops passed by
and stopped those men from killing you.
We have no choice but to
file a case against you.
Your case is no joke.
You entered someone else's house
and harassed that thug's wife.
Chief, that's not true!
You don't understand. That's our house!
Looks like you are under
the influence of alcohol.
What did you take?
What are you saying?
Maybe you should sober up first.
Donaire, bring him in until he sobers up.
Wait, wait, Sir! Sir...
- Bring him in.
- Sir, Sir!
I didn't do anything wrong!
- Come on.
- Sir, Sir! Where are you bringing me?
Hey, hey, hey!
- Hey, Sir! Sir, I don't want to go to jail.
- Hurry up.
Sir!
I have never been imprisoned my whole life!
Sir, I don't like that woman!
My wife is more beautiful!
You're so out of it. Put him inside.
What do you mean?
- Sir!
- Get in!
Boss, boss. Maybe we can talk about this.
Sir, please!
Sir! Boss!
Sir! Sir, please!
Sir, let me out.
Boss.
He's been acting weird, Ma'am.
I'm worried about his situation right now.
He hasn't come back yet.
This one feels different.
It seems something is wrong.
I hope I'm wrong, Ma'am.
You should check on him.
Make sure that he's okay.
Kid, you can get out now.
Liam, son.
Mom?
How...
- Mom.
- Wait.
- What's going on?
- Is this real?
Mom? Is this real?
Am I dreaming?
Mom...
Liam, what's happening to you?
You act like we haven't seen each other
in a long time.
Mama...
There was never a day that
I didn't wish to be with you.
Son...
Why?
What happened?
Mom.
- Mama...
- What happened to you, son?
Mama, Mama...
Liam.
Mama.
Why?
My classmate told me you're sick, Mama.
He said I might not see you anymore.
That's not true.
And...
if ever I'm gone,
I will still watch over you.
All you have to do
is write down everything you want to say.
That way,
I will know what's inside your heart.
Because I will make
all your wishes come true.
What are you talking about?
Oh, my dear.
Mom, I love you so much.
I love you so much, Mom.
So much. So much.
I love you so much. I missed you so much.
Liam, come on.
You talk as if I'm going to disappear.
Joyce... and Dex.
I need to wake up from this dream.
This is not real. This is not real.
This is not real.
I need to wake up from this dream.
- This is not real.
- Liam?
Not real.
Son...
No... This is not real.
Liam...
Liam!
I will wake up.
I will wake up from this nightmare!
Joyce!
Dex!
Joyce...
What the...
Hello, love.
How are you feeling?
Liam, son!
What the...
Hello, love.
How are you feeling?
Who are you?
Love?
Doc, is it possible
that my son got disoriented
after he got into a fight and got beaten up?
He was so confused last night.
He did not know what was happening
and was saying all sorts of things.
I couldn't understand.
It's possible if he got punched rather hard.
He suffers what we call
the "effect of concussions".
You said he lost consciousness,
and now, from what I can observe...
He's dizzy
and looks like there's a loss of memory.
Love.
What were you thinking?
Why did you get into a fight?
And what were you doing
in the middle of the road?
We almost hit you.
Your girlfriend asked
how you were doing last night.
Girlfriend?
Yeah, your girlfriend called.
So I told her I would pick you up
at the police station.
Dear, I'm sorry.
I took your time.
It's okay, Auntie.
Don't worry about it. We're family.
What's important is we had Liam
checked by a doctor.
Doc, thank you for coming.
Anytime, Via.
But I guess we should bring him
to the hospital for possible tests.
What do you think, son? Let's go?
Let's go to the hospital first?
Okay?
Where's the bathroom?
What?
Over there, love.
What really is happening?
If only I could erase the past...
if only I could turn back time...
Is this because of the typewriter?
Is it true?
Liam?
I can't hear him. The faucet is too loud.
If he's throwing up,
we should bring him to the hospital.
Oh my gosh.
Liam!
Liam, are you throwing up?
What? Why?
- Mom...
- What?
Do you remember your typewriter?
What typewriter?
It's a...
It's with the other stuff
we left in Dad's care
after our house burned down.
Oh, if you're looking for our old stuff,
I took them back from Danilo.
They're in our stockroom.
They're in our house?
Even the typewriter is there?
Then let's go. Let's check it out.
Wait, wait.
Where do we live?
Liam.
- I really don't know.
- Liam, come on, let's go.
I thought everything was just a dream
and I would wake up back to reality.
But this is a different reality.
And who is this beautiful woman?
They say she's my girlfriend.
How did it happen?
Liam.
What?
Via, I'll bring Liam home for now.
- Okay, Auntie.
- Yeah.
I'm sorry for bothering you.
It's okay.
Come on, let's go.
You said you had to find something at home?
Let's go? Come on.
- I'll keep you updated, okay?
- Okay, Auntie.
Let's go, Liam.
Is this our house, Mom?
Looks like you really got injured
from the fight.
Yes, this is our house.
You bought it for me.
This was a surprise gift you gave me
when I got out of the hospital
after I had the surgery.
I gave you this house?
Yes, Liam.
I also paid for your surgery?
Does it mean I have lots of money, Mom?
I don't ask you how much you make, Liam.
Yeah.
Well... well...
The stockroom you're talking about, Mom...
Where is it?
- The stockroom?
- Yes.
Over there.
Wait here.
Liam?
Mom, the typewriter isn't here.
Where could it be?
These are all the things
we were able to save.
I didn't notice the missing typewriter.
Mom, I need to find it.
Liam, it doesn't work anymore.
From what I remember, it's already old.
Your great, great grandfather had it way back
during the Japanese occupation.
No one has been using it.
We already have cellphones and computers.
What would you need a typewriter for?
Where is it?
Why are you suddenly looking for it?
I know!
Why don't you try asking your father?
He was the one who offered
to keep the things we salvaged.
I'm just not sure if he kept it properly.
Maybe he has it. I don't know.
Mom, can you go with me there?
Where?
To Dad.
Oh.
Hard pass.
No!
No. I don't want to see your father.
We might get into a fight again.
So, no.
You better go there alone.
You're always there anyway.
I'm always at his house?
Yes.
You do your work at his mansion
whenever you can't finish it at the office,
don't you?
I work at his company?
Liam...
Liam, maybe we need to go to the hospital.
Looks like you have a serious case
of memory loss.
- Let's go to the hospital first?
- Mom, hold on.
- What?
- Wait, just wait.
Liam!
Get some rest first!
Liam.
Gosh, this kid.
Dad!
Anybody home?
Sir Liam.
Sir Danilo and Sir Vergil aren't home yet.
Come in.
Okay.
Have you seen an antique typewriter around?
Are you looking for
your mom's old typewriter?
Yes, Dad.
You should talk to your brother about that.
Vergil turned the old stockroom
into his home office.
Dad told me to ask you
about my mom's old typewriter.
Are you trying to be a junk collector now?
That's nice.
Keep on doing that. You're doing a good job.
I need the typewriter right now.
I need to see it now.
My mom told me you guys might have kept it
after our house burned down.
You think this is the lost-and-found?
Your bastard child is really something, Dad.
Stop, you two.
You're fighting over a useless typewriter.
If you're looking for the rusty typewriter,
it's gone.
I threw it away.
What? Why did you throw it away?
Are you out of your mind?
Didn't you say you no longer needed it
when you and your mom retrieved your things?
What do you expect me to do with it?
We don't collect dust here.
Where did you throw it?
Is there a junk collector around?
Or did you bring it to a junk shop?
Liam, what's with you?
When it's gone, it's gone.
It's a useless typewriter.
You barge in here
looking for that old typewriter.
You didn't even offer an explanation.
I waited for you in our meeting
with the new client in Casa Fuerte.
You didn't come!
You didn't even say a thing!
I asked Borj where you were.
He said you were going through something.
Based on his look,
he seems to be going through
something serious.
Or rather, he was seriously hit on the face.
If you're going through something,
set an appointment
with the company psychiatrist.
Get your act together!
You better be ready for the
groundbreaking ceremony of our new project.
Joyce, Dex, I don't know where you are.
I promise I'll do everything to find you.
[Joycelyn Trinidad Herrera]
[Dexter Trinidad Herrera]
Liam.
I knew you'll come back to this place.
Liam... You know...
I don't understand what's going on.
I don't know.
But I understand
if you're still uncomfortable
opening up to me.
Just always remember, I'm here.
I'm always here for you, Liam.
My son...
Mom.
Mom, thank you.
Thank you for being here.
I love you so much.
So much.
Liam...
Mom...
I hope you don't think that I'm unhappy.
I'm so happy you're alive and with me.
But I know that something's missing.
[Alternate timeline / alternate reality]
[Search more]
[Alternate Reality Fiction]
[Comics, movies and more!]
[The Theory of 2 Worlds]
[Best Fiction Stories]
Fictional stories.
This only happens in comics or in movies.
How is it happening to me?
[Antique Typewriters Philippines]
[Magical Antique Typewriters Philippines]
[No results found]
[Incoming Call: Love]
[Connecting...]
Hi, love.
How are you?
- Hi.
- I'm still worried about you.
I'm doing fine.
That's good to hear.
That's all I wanted to know.
That's why I called.
- Good night, love.
- Good night.
I love you.
Via?
Maybe I really suffered a concussion.
I'm sorry if I was weird when I woke up.
I can't really remember anything.
But, we met when...
Fine.
I won't put anything into this,
except for your head injury.
This is a big day for my brother.
Groundbreaking ceremony.
The biggest mall in Asia.
Your life changed.
And we were dragged into it!
- Liam!
- To the man of the hour.
The great and hard-working congressman.
Where's the rest of the money
from the transaction in Magallanes?
That's 20 million pesos.
Do you think I forgot about it?
You probably haven't heard,
but Sir Liam has a degree
in Creative Writing.
And in this world where I feel trapped,
I'm thankful that I found you again.